[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 15]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
Tinglan.
Lawyer Xiao.
I'm sorry.
I didn't hear you just now.
Why are you so absent-minded lately?
Is something wrong at home?
Maybe I just haven't been
sleeping well lately.
You've worked hard recently.
When the project is over,
I'll give you a few extra days off.
Thank you, Lawyer Xiao.
This...
Lawyer Xiao,
does your family use
Zhuoyuan Technology's products?
How do you feel?
I felt really good.
Ms. Wen said
if there are any problems during use,
we can report them
to the technical department,
and they will debug it again.
Zhao,
pull up last month's user error reports.
Let me take a look.
Okay, Ms. Wen.
[Check if the users have existed.]
[Check the password format]
Look, Ms. Wen.
What about this week's data?
Filter it separately.
Okay.
[Electronic Lock System is completed.]
[Verification user password is correct]
[function statement]
Ms. Wen.
Make a separate copy
of this week's data for me.
Well...
I need to take it with me to check.
Okay.
Done, Ms. Wen.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[Let everyone
enjoy the fun of technology.]
[Call] [Nannan]
[Nannan]
[Contact] [Zhuo Yu'an]
[Zhuo Yu'an]
[Tinglan]
Hello, Tinglan.
Why are you still up so late?
Hello.
Did something happen?
Zhuo Yu'an.
Are you busy?
I'm on a business trip overseas.
Never mind then.
Get back to work.
Wait.
Did something happen
on your end?
Can you hear
my doorbell ringing constantly?
Not just the doorbell,
the TV is making noise too.
No.
Not in the house.
It's in my head.
Tinglan.
Calm down first.
Then I won't hang up.
Try to get some sleep.
I can't close my eyes.
Someone is watching me.
It's okay.
You don't have to sleep yet.
I'll stay here and chat with you.
Okay.
[Zhuo Yu'an]
Tinglan.
On my way to work today,
I saw a kind of bird.
It was a gray bird.
It flew past the car window
and quickly flew away.
It's not a bird we usually see in Senzhou,
but in Qining.
It always flies to our window
in the summer.
[Outpatient]
For the past month or so,
Have you been experiencing insomnia
and auditory hallucinations?
Yes.
I have trouble falling asleep.
In the corners of my house,
I always feel like someone is hiding.
Sometimes when I go out,
I feel like they're following me.
Are there any major changes
in your life recently?
Doctor,
my mom has this condition too.
Could it be hereditary?
Your mother's illness was caused by
external stimuli,
so it's not hereditary.
I can prescribe you some
tranquilizers.
When you have time,
go to the park to get some sun
and relax.
If the symptoms don't improve,
come back for a follow-up.
Yeah.
You've made a lot of progress lately.
Yeah, you skate pretty well too.
We can learn together next time.
♪ I'll wait for you in the crowd ♪
♪ Hearts in sync—how incredible ♪
Yi Muyang, what are you looking at?
Yi Muyang.
Yi Muyang!
♪ It's the cloak of a close embrace ♪
Hi
♪ It's the steadfast days and
nights we share ♪
Do you remember me?
♪ When we weather the storm together,
don't forget ♪
♪ Breathing in the long river of time ♪
You're the kind person
in the street that day.
That's a unique nickname.
♪ My only promise is to you ♪
My name is Yi Muyang.
"Yang" means the rising sun.
♪ Between us ♪
♪ Suspicion feels so far away ♪
♪ When our eyes meet,
I feel your burning gaze ♪
♪ The wind by the shore has stilled ♪
Thank you.
♪ And you're smiling too ♪
Are you okay?
♪ Make a wish to the wind ♪
You
♪ It's Cupid's arrow,
set loose from the string ♪
don't live around here, do you?
I haven't seen you here before.
Right.
I came here on business today,
just to clear my mind.
You really should clear your mind.
Every time I see you,
you don't look very happy.
♪ I'll wait for you in the crowd ♪
Yi Muyang.
Want to try?
♪ Hearts in sync—how incredible ♪
Let me teach you
I...
You guys go ahead and play.
I'm really not good at sports.
♪ It's the familiar breath we share ♪
Are you sure you don't want to try?
It's a lot of fun.
Alright.
♪ It's being each other's exception ♪
Then watch me skate.
By the way,
what's your name?
♪ When tides ebb and flow, I look to you ♪
My name is Shu Tinglan.
Shu Tinglan.
♪ Drowning in the long river of time ♪
When I'm in a bad mood, I eat candy.
I feel much better after eating it.
♪ You're the only air I breathe ♪
Thank you.
♪ Between us ♪
♪ The image of us holding each other ♪
♪ I see the dream encounter of that day ♪
The rain outside the window stopped
We're still here
Tinglan
Tinglan!
Be careful!
♪ Then I met you, in this moment ♪
♪ Like drifting into a dream ♪
♪ In the dream, stars carry a boat
toward the shore ♪
♪ Your faint light lingers ♪
♪ Spreading a warm current
through my heart ♪
♪ Our eyes meet ♪
♪ Bit by bit, healing the wounds ♪
♪ I fear when the dream ends ♪
♪ I'll have to let go of that tenderness ♪